So as you see these are the tools, we also have layers over here.
So for example, if I use the text in order to add up a text over here.
So I use, I choose one of these presets for example.
You will see that when the text is added, a layer will be added on top of my other layers
over here in the layers panel, right? So I wait a little bit.
And as you see, yes, we have these three layers either over here and using the
text tool, I'll be able to click and let's say the example,
I want to change the text to some of that. Yeah, I just need to click a couple times and I'll be able
to edit, right? So for example, I say, we are the, and over here, I say, we are the, we are the
take, take of college, right? For example, and as you see, these preset text are editable as well,
or we can even add our own text box, you know, and have our settings, phone, family,
feel, size, line spacing, et cetera, all of that, right?